[
    { "question" : "vara", "answer" : "to be", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvaːra/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ha", "answer" : "to have", "pronunciation" : "/haː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "göra", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/ˈjøːra/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "säga", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsɛːɡa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "se", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/seː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vilja", "answer" : "to want", "pronunciation" : "/²vɪlja/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "kunna", "answer" : "to be able to", "pronunciation" : "/²kɵnːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ta", "answer" : "to take", "pronunciation" : "/ta/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "få", "answer" : "to get", "pronunciation" : "/foː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "komma", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "/²kɔmːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "stå", "answer" : "to stand", "pronunciation" : "/stoː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ge", "answer" : "to give", "pronunciation" : "/jeː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vet", "answer" : "to know", "pronunciation" : "/veːt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "le", "answer" : "to laugh", "pronunciation" : "/leː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "hitta", "answer" : "to find", "pronunciation" : "/ˈhɪtˌa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "gå", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/ɡoː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "tänka", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/²tɛŋːka/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "känna", "answer" : "to feel", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɕɛn.na/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "behöva", "answer" : "to need", "pronunciation" : "/²bɛːhøːva/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "jobba", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/²jɔbːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "börja", "answer" : "to start", "pronunciation" : "/²bœ̞rˌja/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "sätta", "answer" : "to put", "pronunciation" : "/²sɛtːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "tycka", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/²tʏkːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "leva", "answer" : "to live", "pronunciation" : "/²leːva/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "lita", "answer" : "to trust", "pronunciation" : "/²liːta/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "veta", "answer" : "to know", "pronunciation" : "/²veːta/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "betyda", "answer" : "to mean", "pronunciation" : "/²bɛtyːda/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "räcka", "answer" : "to be enough", "pronunciation" : "/²rɛkːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "visa", "answer" : "to show", "pronunciation" : "/²viːsa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "spela", "answer" : "to play", "pronunciation" : "/²speːla/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "bli", "answer" : "to become", "pronunciation" : "/bliː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "tycka om", "answer" : "to like", "pronunciation" : "/²tʏkːa ɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "fortsätta", "answer" : "to continue", "pronunciation" : "/fɔrtsɛ²tʏːta/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "kalla", "answer" : "to call", "pronunciation" : "/²kalːa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "laga", "answer" : "to fix", "pronunciation" : "/²laːɡa/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "bry sig om", "answer" : "to care about", "pronunciation" : "/bryː sɛj ɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "skriva", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "/²skriːva/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "lämna", "answer" : "to leave", "pronunciation" : "/²lɛmːna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "älska", "answer" : "to love", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɛlˌska/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "använda", "answer" : "to use", "pronunciation" : "/ˈanˌvɛnda/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vända", "answer" : "to turn", "pronunciation" : "/²vɛnːda/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Bok", "answer" : "Book", "pronunciation" : "/bʊk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Bil", "answer" : "Car", "pronunciation" : "/bɪl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Mat", "answer" : "Food", "pronunciation" : "/mat/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Hus", "answer" : "House", "pronunciation" : "/hʉːs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Dag", "answer" : "Day", "pronunciation" : "/dɑːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Träd", "answer" : "Tree", "pronunciation" : "/trɛːd/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Frukost", "answer" : "Breakfast", "pronunciation" : "/frʉːkɔst/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Katt", "answer" : "Cat", "pronunciation" : "/kat/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Hund", "answer" : "Dog", "pronunciation" : "/hɵnd/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Vatten", "answer" : "Water", "pronunciation" : "/vatːɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Sol", "answer" : "Sun", "pronunciation" : "/suːl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Fisk", "answer" : "Fish", "pronunciation" : "/fɪsk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Vägg", "answer" : "Wall", "pronunciation" : "/vɛɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kaffe", "answer" : "Coffee", "pronunciation" : "/kafːɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Ögon", "answer" : "Eyes", "pronunciation" : "/ˈøːɡɔn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Stol", "answer" : "Chair", "pronunciation" : "/stuːl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Fönster", "answer" : "Window", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfœnːstɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Papper", "answer" : "Paper", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpapːɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Dörr", "answer" : "Door", "pronunciation" : "/dœr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Tidning", "answer" : "Newspaper", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtiːdnɪŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Mjölk", "answer" : "Milk", "pronunciation" : "/mjœlk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Cykel", "answer" : "Bicycle", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsyːkɛl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Säng", "answer" : "Bed", "pronunciation" : "/sɛŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Hand", "answer" : "Hand", "pronunciation" : "/hɑːnd/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Klocka", "answer" : "Clock", "pronunciation" : "/ˈklɔkːa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Skola", "answer" : "School", "pronunciation" : "/ˈskuːla/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Frukt", "answer" : "Fruit", "pronunciation" : "/frʉkt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Väder", "answer" : "Weather", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɛːdɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Väg", "answer" : "Road", "pronunciation" : "/vɛːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kruka", "answer" : "Pot", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkrʉːka/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Park", "answer" : "Park", "pronunciation" : "/pɑːrk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Musik", "answer" : "Music", "pronunciation" : "/mʉːsɪk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Hår", "answer" : "Hair", "pronunciation" : "/hoːr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Lampa", "answer" : "Lamp", "pronunciation" : "/ˈlamːpa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Sjö", "answer" : "Lake", "pronunciation" : "/ɧøː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Maträtt", "answer" : "Dish", "pronunciation" : "/mɑːtrɛtː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Natt", "answer" : "Night", "pronunciation" : "/nat/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Resa", "answer" : "Trip", "pronunciation" : "/ˈreːsa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Skor", "answer" : "Shoes", "pronunciation" : "/skuːr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Buss", "answer" : "Bus", "pronunciation" : "/bɵsː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Stad", "answer" : "City", "pronunciation" : "/stɑːd/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kläder", "answer" : "Clothes", "pronunciation" : "/klɛːdɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Rök", "answer" : "Smoke", "pronunciation" : "/røːk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Dator", "answer" : "Computer", "pronunciation" : "/dɑːtɔr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Sallad", "answer" : "Salad", "pronunciation" : "/salad/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kök", "answer" : "Kitchen", "pronunciation" : "/ɕœk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Hav", "answer" : "Sea", "pronunciation" : "/hɑːv/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Möbler", "answer" : "Furniture", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmøːblɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Bra", "answer" : "Good", "pronunciation" : "/braː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Liten", "answer" : "Small", "pronunciation" : "/liːtɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Stor", "answer" : "Big", "pronunciation" : "/stuːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Vacker", "answer" : "Beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvakːɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Röd", "answer" : "Red", "pronunciation" : "/røːd/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Blå", "answer" : "Blue", "pronunciation" : "/bloː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Grön", "answer" : "Green", "pronunciation" : "/ɡrøːn/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Gul", "answer" : "Yellow", "pronunciation" : "/ɡɵl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Svart", "answer" : "Black", "pronunciation" : "/svart/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Vit", "answer" : "White", "pronunciation" : "/viːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ny", "answer" : "New", "pronunciation" : "/nyː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Gammal", "answer" : "Old", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɡamːal/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Hög", "answer" : "High", "pronunciation" : "/høːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Låg", "answer" : "Low", "pronunciation" : "/loːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Lätt", "answer" : "Easy", "pronunciation" : "/lɛtː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Svår", "answer" : "Difficult", "pronunciation" : "/svɑːr/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Rolig", "answer" : "Fun", "pronunciation" : "/rɔlɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Tråkig", "answer" : "Boring", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtroːkɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Snabb", "answer" : "Fast", "pronunciation" : "/snabː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Lång", "answer" : "Long", "pronunciation" : "/loːŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Kort", "answer" : "Short", "pronunciation" : "/kɔʈ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Tung", "answer" : "Heavy", "pronunciation" : "/tɵŋ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ljus", "answer" : "Light", "pronunciation" : "/jʉːs/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Mörk", "answer" : "Dark", "pronunciation" : "/mœrːk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Stark", "answer" : "Strong", "pronunciation" : "/starːk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Svag", "answer" : "Weak", "pronunciation" : "/svɑːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Söt", "answer" : "Sweet", "pronunciation" : "/søːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Salt", "answer" : "Salty", "pronunciation" : "/sɑlt/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Surt", "answer" : "Sour", "pronunciation" : "/sɵʈ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Besviken", "answer" : "Disappointed", "pronunciation" : "/bɛsˈviːkɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Nöjd", "answer" : "Satisfied", "pronunciation" : "/nœjd/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Glad", "answer" : "Happy", "pronunciation" : "/ɡlad/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ledsen", "answer" : "Sad", "pronunciation" : "/ˈleːdsɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Rik", "answer" : "Rich", "pronunciation" : "/riːk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Fattig", "answer" : "Poor", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfatːɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Rätt", "answer" : "Right", "pronunciation" : "/rɛtː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Fel", "answer" : "Wrong", "pronunciation" : "/feːl/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ren", "answer" : "Clean", "pronunciation" : "/reːn/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Smutsig", "answer" : "Dirty", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsmʉːtsɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ljum", "answer" : "Lukewarm", "pronunciation" : "/jɵm/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Kall", "answer" : "Cold", "pronunciation" : "/kalː/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Varm", "answer" : "Warm", "pronunciation" : "/varm/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Nödvändig", "answer" : "Necessary", "pronunciation" : "/nœdˈvɛnːdɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Onödig", "answer" : "Unnecessary", "pronunciation" : "/ɔˈnøːdɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Häftig", "answer" : "Cool", "pronunciation" : "/ˈhɛfːtɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Känd", "answer" : "Famous", "pronunciation" : "/ɕɛnd/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Här", "answer" : "Here", "pronunciation" : "/hɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Där", "answer" : "There", "pronunciation" : "/dɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Nu", "answer" : "Now", "pronunciation" : "/nuː/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Snabbt", "answer" : "Quickly", "pronunciation" : "/snabːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Långsamt", "answer" : "Slowly", "pronunciation" : "/loːŋsamt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Aldrig", "answer" : "Never", "pronunciation" : "/ˈalːdrɪɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Alltid", "answer" : "Always", "pronunciation" : "/alːtɪd/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Bara", "answer" : "Only", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbɑːra/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Redan", "answer" : "Already", "pronunciation" : "/rɛˈdɑːn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Senare", "answer" : "Later", "pronunciation" : "/sɛˈnaːrɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Fortfarande", "answer" : "Still", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfɔrtfaranːdɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Ibland", "answer" : "Sometimes", "pronunciation" : "/ɪˈblanːd/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Vanligtvis", "answer" : "Usually", "pronunciation" : "/vanlɪktvɪs/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Sällan", "answer" : "Rarely", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsɛlːan/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Faktiskt", "answer" : "Actually", "pronunciation" : "/fakˈtɪskt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Tyvärr", "answer" : "Unfortunately", "pronunciation" : "/tʏˈvɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Visserligen", "answer" : "Indeed", "pronunciation" : "/vɪsɛrˈliːɡɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Förmodligen", "answer" : "Probably", "pronunciation" : "/fœrˈmɔdliːɡɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Verkligen", "answer" : "Really", "pronunciation" : "/vɛrkˈliːɡɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Snart", "answer" : "Soon", "pronunciation" : "/snɑːrt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Precis", "answer" : "Exactly", "pronunciation" : "/prɛsiːs/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Vanligtvis", "answer" : "Usually", "pronunciation" : "/vanlɪktvɪs/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Mycket", "answer" : "Very", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmykːɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Lite", "answer" : "A little bit", "pronunciation" : "/ˈliːtɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Alldeles", "answer" : "Completely", "pronunciation" : "/ˈalːdɛlɛs/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Kanske", "answer" : "Perhaps", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkanːsɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Så", "answer" : "So", "pronunciation" : "/soː/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Gärna", "answer" : "Gladly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈjæːrna/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Hemma", "answer" : "At home", "pronunciation" : "/ˈhɛmːa/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Borta", "answer" : "Away", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbɔrːta/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Förrän", "answer" : "Until", "pronunciation" : "/fœrˈrɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Ofta", "answer" : "Often", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɔfːta/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Emellanåt", "answer" : "Occasionally", "pronunciation" : "/ɛmɛlanˈoːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Nog", "answer" : "Enough", "pronunciation" : "/nuːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Inom kort", "answer" : "Shortly", "pronunciation" : "/ɪnɔm kɔrt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Överallt", "answer" : "Everywhere", "pronunciation" : "/øvɛralːt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Ingenstans", "answer" : "Nowhere", "pronunciation" : "/ɪŋɛnˌstanːs/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Någonsin", "answer" : "Ever", "pronunciation" : "/ˈnoːɡɔnsɪn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Och", "answer" : "And", "pronunciation" : "/ɔk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Men", "answer" : "But", "pronunciation" : "/meːn/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Eller", "answer" : "Or", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɛlːɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "För", "answer" : "For", "pronunciation" : "/fœr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Så", "answer" : "So", "pronunciation" : "/soː/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Att", "answer" : "That", "pronunciation" : "/atː/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Eftersom", "answer" : "Since", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɛfːtɛrsɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "När", "answer" : "When", "pronunciation" : "/nɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Om", "answer" : "If", "pronunciation" : "/ɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Medan", "answer" : "While", "pronunciation" : "/meːdan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Trots att", "answer" : "Although", "pronunciation" : "/trɔts at/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Även om", "answer" : "Even though", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɛːvɛn ɔm/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Därför att", "answer" : "Because", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdɛrːfœr at/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Sedan", "answer" : "Since", "pronunciation" : "/ˈseːdan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Innan", "answer" : "Before", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɪnːan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Så att", "answer" : "So that", "pronunciation" : "/soː at/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Utan", "answer" : "Without", "pronunciation" : "/ʉːtan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Då", "answer" : "When", "pronunciation" : "/doː/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Fast", "answer" : "Although", "pronunciation" : "/fast/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Att", "answer" : "To", "pronunciation" : "/atː/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Emellertid", "answer" : "However", "pronunciation" : "/ɛmɛlɛrˈtiːd/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Så länge", "answer" : "As long as", "pronunciation" : "/soː lɛŋːɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Så snart", "answer" : "As soon as", "pronunciation" : "/soː snɑːrt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "För att", "answer" : "In order to", "pronunciation" : "/fœr at/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "När som helst", "answer" : "Anytime", "pronunciation" : "/nɛr sɔm hɛlst/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Huruvida", "answer" : "Whether", "pronunciation" : "/hɵrɵviːda/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Antingen eller", "answer" : "Either or", "pronunciation" : "/ˈanːtɪŋɛn ˈɛlːɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Varken eller", "answer" : "Neither nor", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvarkɛn ˈɛlːɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Dels... dels", "answer" : "Partly", "pronunciation" : "/dɛls dɛls/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Både och", "answer" : "Both and", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbɔdɛ ɔk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "I och för sig", "answer" : "In a way", "pronunciation" : "/ɪ ɔk fœr siːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Emedan", "answer" : "Since", "pronunciation" : "/ɛˈmeːdan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Alltså", "answer" : "Therefore", "pronunciation" : "/ˈalːtso/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Hädanefter", "answer" : "Henceforth", "pronunciation" : "/ˈhɛːdanɛftɛr/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Fram tills", "answer" : "Until", "pronunciation" : "/fram tɪls/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Genom att", "answer" : "By", "pronunciation" : "/ɡɛˈnɔm at/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Därmed", "answer" : "Thus", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdɛrːmɛd/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]